Quiet. they're listening.
How's the count?
Keep it tight.
Pay attention.
Big Lomas has to keep up...
...or they'll green light 'em.
Don't forget
you work for Wizard.
It's under control.
I heard a prison rumor.
What prison rumor?
Another three dead.
Wizard hit the Cartel.
I'm Conejo.
and don't you forget that name.
When you say it.
you say it with respect.
I know who you are.
I know who you're with.
Sometimes people get confused.
They don't know who is who.
Trust me. This...
...is a mistake.
I don't know
where you came from...
...or who you are connected to.
But. clearly. you are somebody.
You're touching something big
right now.
Bigger than me...
...bigger than you.
It is very smart...
...and very cold.
You're just a man.
You breathe...
...and bleed.
And so do the people you love.
Look. go talk to your uncle.
Tell him Conejo
is back from Jalisco.
He knows who I am.
Go back to your big house.
Enjoy your pretty wife
and your two kids.
Yeah. like that.
With all due respect...
...this is a bad play.
Death is after you.
"You whore! You and your kids
should go to hell!"
Did you think
about what we talked about?
Your uncle's been
in this business a long time.
He talks a lot about the past...
...and forgets that we have
a lot of product to move.
But. have you asked yourself:
Why are you only breaking arms
for Wizard?
It's nice to have
a powerful family...
...and royal blood
running through your veins.
Blood protects blood.
The trigger was pulled
years ago.
Gata. show them.
Now Wizard's time is over.
and your world is dying.
If you want to join me.
you're welcome to...
...because you do your job well.
I can take care of you...
...and make you richer
than you ever imagined.
But Wizard doesn't talk to you.
does he?
I'm here to prepare for war.
Protect me from the bullets
of my enemies.
Make me invisible
to the government's eyes.
Make my heart strong...
...because I'm here
to take it all.
Move. let's get
what we came for.
Gata. bring her to me.
Let's get this over with...
...and send these motherfuckers
to hell.
You'll beg
for a bullet in the head.
Primo. bring him.
We'll throw this bitch a party.
My messages on my phone.
Conejo...
I know where he is.
You're going to die.
Don't you know I have
the protection of the devil?
For my family. I live.
For my family. I die.
For my family...
...I kill.
My son.
But it wants you. son.